A moment ago, you turned off the TV
in the middle of the Deep Space Nine...
...Star Trek: The Original Series
"Trouble With Tribbles" crossover episode.
(Sheldon:)Would you like some advice?
(Leonard:)Sure, why not?
(Sheldon:)Then this is the perfect time
to launch a blog...
(Sheldon:)...with an interactive comments section.
(Leonard:)Gee, thanks a lot.
(Sheldon:)Would you rather I offer
my personal insight?
No, I don't need any insights.
I just wanna know why Penny's
more interested in Stuart than me.
(Leonard:)We're practically the same guy.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I disagree.
You know, Stuart is taller,
artistic, self-employed...
(Sheldon:)...and, most significantly,
he gets 45 percent off comic books.
(Leonard:)You're right. I really should be asking
strangers on the Internet.
(Sheldon:)My original point.
(Sheldon:)Chinese food, vintage video games.